{
    "id": "4f93038c3ce44d678965501a6de55bb6",
    "title": "Infinitives worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4f1076bb552d41e9b778a098b0107c97",
            "title": "Infinitives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Rahul …………… ……………… the letter yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "forgot, posting",
                        "forgot, to post",
                        "forgot, posted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………… him why he ........................ angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "asked, is",
                        "asked, was",
                        "ask, was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor ………………. the patient …………………. his medicines without fail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "advised, to take",
                        "advised, taking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………..  for someone …………….. the lawn.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "look, mow",
                        "looking, to mow",
                        "are looking, to mow",
                        "are looking, mowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "All the students ………………. …………………. in the program.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want, to participate",
                        "want, participating",
                        "want, participate"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………….. to the airport ……………… off my friend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went, see",
                        "went, to see",
                        "went, seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bear ……………….. up the tree ………………. the honey.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "climbing, to drink",
                        "climbed, to drink",
                        "climbed, drinking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Last month we ……………… to Agra ……………. the Taj Mahal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went, seeing",
                        "went, to see",
                        "went, saw"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher ……………… the students ……………. hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "encouraging, working",
                        "encouraged, working",
                        "encouraged, to work"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. ………………. the first prize in the quiz competition.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want, to win",
                        "am wanting, to win",
                        "want, winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}